<?xml version="1.0"?>
<articles>
<article>
<id>75806ec6-ede5-47ef-be71-e34280cdb294</id>
<media_type>Print</media_type>
<title><![CDATA[THE MIELE DIALOG OVEN'S IFA DEBUT]]></title>
<outlet>DEALERSCOPE</outlet>
<journalist><![CDATA[NANCY KLOSEK]]></journalist>
<pubvalue>11534.9000</pubvalue>
<content_summary><![CDATA[BY   One of the more unique product introductions at the recent IFA Berlin Show last month was made by appliance maker Miele. The ...]]></content_summary>
<content_date>11/1/2017</content_date>
<content_url><![CDATA[http://images.burrellesluce.com/image/2253DA/2253DA_14528]]></content_url>
<city>PHILADELPHIA</city>
<state>PA</state>
<body><![CDATA[<p>THE MIELE DIALOG OVEN'S IFA DEBUT</p>THE MIELE DIALOG OVEN'S IFA DEBUT  BY NANCY KLOSEK  One of the more unique product introductions at the recent IFA Berlin Show last month was made by appliance maker Miele. The introduction was arguably characterized by Markus Miele, the company's executive director and co-proprietor, as "the biggest technological advance since the launch of induction cooking." It was the Dialog oven, which uses Miele's M Chef technology and the volumetric cooking method.  Twin electromagnetic wave antennas receive intermittent readings every 10 seconds on how much of transmitted cooking energy has been absorbed by the food, and a sensor adjusts temperatures accordingly.  sometimes cutting cooking time by up to 70 percent.  The company demonstrated the Dialog's efficacy at its introduction by fully cooking a raw cod fillet encased in a block of ice - extraordinarily, without melting any of the ice. It also showed how, theoretically, a loaf of bread could be fully cooked without generating a crust (although I can't think why anyone would want to do that, except for the reason that it could be done).  The oven can also cook multiple meal elements such as steak, asparagus and potatoes simultaneously on a single plate, without shortchanging or overcooking any  of the food elements - and Miele says cooking time using this method is cut dramatically; for example, the Dialog can cook pulled pork within 2 -1/2 hours versus the usual eight hours.  The oven is designed with an exceptionally thick door to ensure electromagnetic interference suppression. It also comes loaded with 100 programs on board and is also workable via the Miele mobile app. Market launch was initially slated for Spring 2018 in Europe, but the company also has a solid foothold in The States with its line of premium appliances, so stay tuned. ¦  A FULLY COOKED CODFISH EMERGES FROM THE ICE BLOCK IT WAS COOKED IN  THE MIELE DIALOG OVEN  MULTIPLE FOODS MAY BE COOKED SIMULTANEOUSLY WITH THE VOLUMETRIC COOKING METHOD  MARKUS MIELE (RIGHT), LOOKS ON AS A CHEF MEASURES ICE BLOCK TEMPERATURE]]></body>
</article>
<article>
<id>34ab52ca-ca2d-410d-8554-a2ae63d6a674</id>
<media_type>Print</media_type>
<title><![CDATA[Black Friday: What to buy and what to skip]]></title>
<outlet>METRO NEW YORK</outlet>
<journalist><![CDATA[Courtney Jespersen]]></journalist>
<pubvalue>17912.8000</pubvalue>
<content_summary><![CDATA[As you plan out your Black Friday deal-hunting, stick to these shopping categories to get the biggest hang for your buck, btock  Use ...]]></content_summary>
<content_date>11/21/2017</content_date>
<content_url><![CDATA[http://images.burrellesluce.com/image/2253DX/2253DX_2835]]></content_url>
<city>NEW YORK</city>
<state>NY</state>
<body><![CDATA[<p>Black Friday: What to buy and what to skip</p>Black Friday: What to buy and what to skip  As you plan out your Black Friday deal-hunting, stick to these shopping categories to get the biggest hang for your buck, btock  Use this guide to steer clear ofthe duds and get only the best bargains this Nov. 24.  >  NerdWalletisa personal finance website.  Buy: Apple products  Traditionally, major retail stores such as Best Buy, Target and Walmart discount Apple products each year on Black Friday, and previous-generation models usually see the most dramatic deals. These offers may include price cuts, free gift cards with purchase or a combination of both. This year, look for deals on MacBooks, iMacs, iPhones, iPads, Apple Watches and Apple TVs. Target devoted an entire page of its 2016 Black Friday ad to Apple. All iPod models were 20% off, and the Apple Watch Series 1 started at $198.  Skip: Toys  Toys are one ofthe seasonal purchase staples,  but you might want to think twice before checking them off your list on Black Friday. Historically, it's best to wait until closer to Christmas to purchase dolls, action figures and play sets. You run the risk that certain items will sell out, but you may also be able to find bigger savings on what's left  Last year, in the final days before Christmas, select toys were on sale for as much as 50% off.  Buy: Video games, CDs, DVDs  If you're in need of some affordable stocking stuffcrs, look no further than the video game, CD, DVD and Blu-ray department at most major retailers this Black Friday. You'll find films and gaming titles deeply discounted from their original prices.  In 2016, Best Buy offered select Bluray+DVD+digital titles for $7.99 each. Walmart had certain video games for $27 each and a selection of over 200 DVD titles for $1.96 apiece.  Skip: Christmas decorations  You've likely seen the blowout post-Christmas clearance sales everv  year on Dec. 26 as you made your way to the store to return that gift that missed the mark. That's when Christmas decorations, wrapping paper, tinsel and other seasonal trimmings reach super low prices (for obvious reasons).  If you can't wait until after Christmas, hold off for a little while. Sure, you'll see plenty of deals on artificial trees and rolls of wrapping paper on Black Friday ? especially at home and craft stores ? but retailers are particularly eager to slash prices closer to Dec. 25. In the days leading up to Christmas 2016, Big Lots took 50% off a selection of ornaments and decorations.  Buy: Electronics Electronics deals are a Black Friday staple. In 2016, Walmart offered an impressive $125 deal on a 40-inch Element or Hisense HDTV. Best Buy discounted select Amazon Fire tablets by up to $30.  No matter where you choose to spend your Black Friday (or Thanksgiving), you're almost guaranteed to find TV and tablet doorbusters. Another electronics deal to keep an eye out  for is smartphones. Last year, some retailers offered free gift cards (in amounts as substantial as $250) with a qualifying phone purchase on an installment plan.  Skip: Bedding  You've got the entertainment center covered, but you should hesitate before stocking up on supplies to refresh the look of your bedroom this Black Friday.  The lowest prices on bedding and linens have been known to appear in January during what arc called "white sales," so hold off until then if you can. Discounts at this time can range from 50% to 75%. January 2017 white sales took place at retailers such as Macy's, Kmart, Kohl's and Overstock.  Buy: Home appliances No secret here. Black Friday is well-known for its offers of huge savings on washers, dryers, refrigerators and major kitchen appliances. Look for similar deep discounts again this year. Last year ar Sears, a Kenmore washer and dryer were on sale for $274.99 each when shoppers purchased the pair. That was a 49%  discount on the pair. Best Buy took up to 40% off major appliance top deals, and shoppers got a free Keurig K525 coffee brewer with purchase of two or more major appliances totaling $2,000 and up.  If you're in the market for smaller appliances such as coffee makers, mixers, blenders or vacuum cleaners, expect deals this year from department stores such as Kohl's, J.C. Penney and Macy's.  Skip: Winter clothing Fall and winter clothing generally isn't the best value on Black Friday. Jeans, for instance, see big sales in October, and retailers frequently offer big clearance sales on jackets when winter gives way to spring.  Of course, if you need something to keep you warm before then, you'll be able to find some bargains this Black Friday. Year after year, Macy's and J.C. Penney have offered doorbuster deals on women's boots. In the past, select pairs have been just $19.99 each.  Buy: Travel deals Whether it's hotel rooms, ski lift tickets or airfare, you can expect  bargains on travel this Black Friday and Cyber Monday (Nov. 27). Check for deals from online travel sites and major airlines alike. In the past, most of these promotions were available for a very limited time. You'll likely have to book during that window and travel during an allotted period.  Skip: Mail-in rebates  If you want to avoid some ofthe hassle related to Black Friday shopping, resist deals that require a mail-in rebate. Unless you're disciplined enough to fill out the form and wait to receive the rebate, you could end up paying more than you intended. And even if you do follow through with a rebate, you'll have to shell out a higher price at the register before getting some money back.  Always read the fine print; some kitchen appliances, electronics and other popular items may require you to fill out a mail-in rebate to achieve the advertised price. At Kohl's, for example, some small kitchen appliances were available for $9.99 last year ? but that was after a $12 mail-in rebate, courtneyjespersen]]></body>
</article>
<article>
<id>d9c53d5b-e41e-4037-8c2e-83f9802c7bb0</id>
<media_type>Print</media_type>
<title><![CDATA[Don't get duped on Black Friday]]></title>
<outlet>METRO NEW YORK</outlet>
<journalist><![CDATA[Courtney Jespersen]]></journalist>
<pubvalue>8956.4000</pubvalue>
<content_summary><![CDATA[Learn to identify these common tricks by retailers so that you don't fall for them this year, istock    Like the arrival of Santa's sleigh ...]]></content_summary>
<content_date>11/21/2017</content_date>
<content_url><![CDATA[http://images.burrellesluce.com/image/2253DX/2253DX_2836]]></content_url>
<city>NEW YORK</city>
<state>NY</state>
<body><![CDATA[<p>Don't get duped on Black Friday</p>Learn to identify these common tricks by retailers so that you don't fall for them this year, istock  Don't get duped on Black Friday  Like the arrival of Santa's sleigh on Christmas Eve, each year retailers deliver a host of deals, discounts and freebies for shoppers as part of a highly anticipated shopping event called Black Friday, which falls on the day after Thanksgiving.  Many of the deals are legitimate bargains, but others are nothing more than ordinary sales wrapped in shiny packaging. How can you tell the difference'? We have the secrets you need to know about the annual discount shopping bonanza, which this year is Nov. 24.  l. Doorbusters are few and far between  Doorbusters are the blockbusters of Black Friday. They're deeply discounted products that are available for only a limited window of time ? usually on Thanksgiving Da}' or Black Friday. The products look good, and the prices certainly sound good, but the reality of actually getting your hands on one of these items isn't so rosy.  Most retailers will indicate "limited quantities" beneath certain deals. In 2015, we got a sense for how limited that could be when Sears plastered a Kenmore Elite washer  and dryer on the front page of its Black Friday ad, with the promise of 51% off on the pair. But the fine print below the deal revealed that there were only about four available per store.  The story is similar at other retailers. If you don't secure a spot at the front of the line or log online the moment a sale starts, you could miss your shot at these big deals. Shoppers should look for stores with doorbuster guarantees. In some cases, as long as you arrive at a certain time, you can be guaranteed the low price.  2. Discounts are often  inflated  Deals can be difficult to grab, but they can also be misleading. Last year, a NerdWallet study found that some stores inflated the amount of certain Black Friday discounts to make deals appear better than they actually were.  For instance, at I Iarbor Freight Tools, the 17 Ft. Type 1A Multi-Task Ladder was on sale for $115 during Black Friday 2015. It was $99.99 on Black Friday 2016. In 2015, Harbor Freight Tools contrasted the ladder's sale price with a comp price of$209.99.Butin2016,  the ladder's sale price was accompanied by a previous price of SI 39.99 and a comp price of $357.99.  The 2016 deal was indeed a lower price, but because of the comp price reflected next to the deal, the savings appeared more substantial.  If you shop this year on Black Friday, don't pay attention to the supposed percentage of the discounts. Instead, judge the value of a product based on the sale price and how it compares with the item's price at other stores.  3. Fine print is everywhere  Finally, even if you manage to avoid all of the above tricks and traps, you could still be faced with more fine print. Retailers have a way of making some sales difficult to actually claim.  Certain products are available at their advertised sale price only for a few hours and then go up in price. Keep an eye out for such fine print and exclusions ? usually located at the bottom of a Black Friday ad or beneath individual deals vvithin the ad ? so you aren't suiprised when you get to the store on Black Friday, couktneyjespersen]]></body>
</article>
<article>
<id>dd88148a-8c8a-4ce2-baa1-7a23a0373404</id>
<media_type>Print</media_type>
<title><![CDATA[Choosing sides]]></title>
<outlet>O-D(OBSERVER-DISPATCH)</outlet>
<journalist><![CDATA[Anne D'Innocenzio]]></journalist>
<pubvalue>1296.7500</pubvalue>
<content_summary><![CDATA[Amazon or Walmart? Some retailers are making alliances  By   The Associated Press  NEW YORK - Store chains feeling the upheaval in ...]]></content_summary>
<content_date>11/15/2017</content_date>
<content_url><![CDATA[http://images.burrellesluce.com/image/2253DA/2253DA_14510]]></content_url>
<city>UTICA</city>
<state>NY</state>
<body><![CDATA[<p>Choosing sides</p>Choosing sides  Amazon or Walmart? Some retailers are making alliances  By Anne D'Innocenzio  The Associated Press  NEW YORK - Store chains feeling the upheaval in retail are making strategic alliances - and that can mean picking sides.  Kohl's shoppers can find Amazon devices at some stores, and return items they bought from the online retailer. Nike has made some of its sneakers available through Amazon. The owner of Sears is selling Kenmorebranded appliances on Amazon in some markets. And Best Buy is teaming up with Amazon for voice shopping.  Meanwhile, Walmart, which has the most store locations, is assembling a coalition of its own: buying smaller online brands and becoming the highest-profile partner to Google in voice shopping. And the discount chain that touts low prices announced a web partnership Monday with high-end department store Lord & Taylor.  "When you are in an historic uncharted chaotic situation, you often see these strange bedfellows," said Joel Bines, co-head of AlixPartners' retail practice and a managing director at the firm.  Since the beginning ofthe year, several retailers have filed for bankruptcy protection, including well-known names like Toys R Us. And retailers have announced thousands of store closings, with more expected. Analysts say some brands realize they might not succeed alone.  "You have to be challenging accepted norms. So you might find partners that you normally wouldn't have considered," said Wendy Liebmann, CEO of WSL Strategic Retail. "This has exploded because of the urgency to change. You look at retailers who are closing or struggling."  So as Amazon moves even further into fashion, home electronics and grocery stores, and cements shopper loyalty with its $oa-a-year Prime membership, stores are developing partnerships with the online retailer to increase customer traffic or expand their offerings online.  At the participating Kohl's stores, shoppers will find l,ooo-square-fo<ot Amazon areas that sell Echos~7 Fire tablets and other gadgets. People can also arrange to have an Amazon employee visit their home and install a device or recommend smart home products to buy. And some stores pack and ship eligible Amazon return items for free. Kohl's hopes the arrangement brings in shoppers who might pick up clothes or home items.  Analysts say other department stores, facing the same kind of issues, could follow.  From its base with 4,700 U.S. stores, Walmart is hning up other partners. In voice shopping, it hooked up with Google, which has signed up other chains such as Target and Home Depot to fight the dominance of Amazon's Alexa-powered Echo devices.  Lord & Taylor's president Liz Rodbell told The Associated Press the arrangement with Walmart allows the chain to attract new customers who already are buying  higher-end products on Walmart. com. She called the partnership "a pivotal moment" for the retailer. It comes after the chain's parent company announced last month it was selling its New York flagship building to We Work and leasing back a portion of the space.  Neither company would say the financial details of the arrangement.  Denise Incandela, head of fashion at Walmart's U.S. e-commerce division, says it's focusing on specialized shopping experiences, starting with fashion. Since the $3 billion-plus acquisition of Jet.com last year, Walmart has bought several online brands like Bonobos and ModCloth.  Analysts say Walmart is developing its own higher-end online mall as a way to counter Amazon's dominance.  Bines said it's a good strategy, since Walmart.com could attract "an entirely different demographic" from the chain's physical stores.  Walmart store customers have a median household income of about $48,000, below the $56,000 for walmart.com customers, according to Craig Johnson, president of the retail consulting group Customer Growth Partners. Amazon.com shoppers have a median income of $85,000, Johnson estimates.  Liebmann says the bigger ques tion is whether there would be any resistance from Lord & Taylor shoppers. Bonobos andModCloth fans complained vociferously on social media when reports were swirling about Walmart's move to buy the brands. "It has to be presented well," Liebmann said.  The Kenmore Elite Smart French Door Refrigerator appears on display at a Sears store July 20 in West Jordan, Utah.  [RICK BOWMER/ASSOCIATED PRESS FILE PHOTO]]]></body>
</article>
<article>
<id>25501c8f-8eb1-4e40-a7ec-8ab42b49d8d9</id>
<media_type>Print</media_type>
<title><![CDATA[Choosing sides]]></title>
<outlet>GASTON GAZETTE</outlet>
<journalist><![CDATA[Anne D'Innocenzio]]></journalist>
<pubvalue>1684.8000</pubvalue>
<content_summary><![CDATA[Amazon or Walmart? Some retailers are making alliances By   The Associated Press  NEW YORK - Store chains feeling the upheaval in retail ...]]></content_summary>
<content_date>11/15/2017</content_date>
<content_url><![CDATA[http://images.burrellesluce.com/image/2253DA/2253DA_14513]]></content_url>
<city>GASTONIA</city>
<state>NC</state>
<body><![CDATA[<p>Choosing sides</p>Choosing sides  Amazon or Walmart? Some retailers are making alliances By Anne D'Innocenzio  The Associated Press  NEW YORK - Store chains feeling the upheaval in retail are making strategic alliances ? and that can mean picking sides.  Kohl's shoppers can find Amazon devices at some stores, and return items they bought from the online retailer. Nike has made some of its sneakers available through Amazon. The owner of Sears is selling Kenmore-branded appliances on Amazon in some markets. And Best Buy is teaming up with Amazon for voice shopping.  Meanwhile, Walmart, whichhas the most store locations, is assembling a coalition of its own: buying smaller online brands and becoming the highest-profile partner to Google in voice shopping. And the discount chain that touts low prices announced a web partnership Monday with high-end department store Lord & Taylor.  "When you are in an historic uncharted chaotic situation, you often see these strange bedfellows," said Joel Bines, co-head of AlixPartners' retail practice and a managing director at the firm.  Since the beginning of the year, several retailers have filed for bankruptcy protection, including well-known  names like Toys R Us. And retailers have announced thousands of store closings, with more expected. Analysts say some brands realize they might not succeed alone.  "You have to be challenging accepted norms. So you might find partners that you normally wouldn't have considered," said Wendy Liebmann, CEO of WSL Strategic Retail. "This has exploded because of the urgency to change. You look at retailers who are closing or struggling."  So as Amazon moves even further into fashion, home electronics and grocery stores, and cements shopper loyalty with its $99-a-year Prime membership, stores are developing partnerships with the online retailer to increase customer traffic or expand their offerings online.  At the participating Kohl's stores, shoppers will find 1,000-square-foot Amazon areas that sell Echos, Fire tablets and other gadgets. People can also arrange to have an Amazon employee visit their home and install a device or recommend smart home products to buy. And some stores pack and ship eligible Amazon return items for free. Kohl's hopes the arrangement brings in shoppers who might pick up clothes or home items.  Analysts say other department stores, facing the same kind of issues, could follow.  From its base with 4,700  U.S. stores, Walmart is lining up other partners. In voice shopping, it hooked up with Google, which has signed up other chains such as Target and Home Depot to fight the dominance of Amazon's Alexa-powered Echo devices.  Lord & Taylor's president Liz Rodbell told The Associated Press the arrangement with Walmart allows the chain to attract new customers who already are buying higher-end products on Walmart.com. She called the partnership "a pivotal moment" for the retailer. It comes after the chain's parent company announced last month it was selling its New York flagship building to We Work and leasing back a portion of the space.  Neither company would say the financial details of the arrangement.  Denise Incandela, head of fashion at Walmart's U.S. e-commerce division, says it's focusing on specialized shopping experiences, starting with fashion. Since the $3 billion-plus acquisition of Jet. com last year, Walmart has bought several online brands like Bonobos and ModCloth.  Analysts say Walmart is developing its own higherend online mall as a way to counter Amazon's dominance. Bines said it's a good strategy, sinceWalmart.com could attract "an entirely different demographic" from the chain's physical stores.  The Kenmore Elite Smart French Door Refrigerator appears on display at a Sears store July 20 in West Jordan, Utah, [rick bowmer/associated press file photo]]]></body>
</article>
<article>
<id>9f54184c-162f-4a21-a952-f08d142c1a41</id>
<media_type>Print</media_type>
<title><![CDATA[Washing Machines]]></title>
<outlet>CONSUMER REPORTS</outlet>
<journalist><![CDATA[]]></journalist>
<pubvalue>0.0000</pubvalue>
<content_summary><![CDATA[Consumer Reports?  2,<  ill  _ RATED %#~_T PRODUCTS  Buying Guide  2018  Cars  TVs  Ranges  Refrigerators  Laptops  Vacuums  Smartphones  ...]]></content_summary>
<content_date>12/15/2017</content_date>
<content_url><![CDATA[http://images.burrellesluce.com/image/2253DA/2253DA_14531]]></content_url>
<city>YONKERS</city>
<state>NY</state>
<body><![CDATA[<p>Washing Machines</p>Consumer Reports?  2,<  ill  _ RATED %#~_T PRODUCTS  Buying Guide  2018  Cars  TVs  Ranges  Refrigerators  Laptops  Vacuums  Smartphones  Gas Grills  And More!  QUICK GUIDE  Washing Machines  Today's washing machines tend to boast larger capacities, so you can do more laundry at once. You'll also find Wi-Fi-enabled models that provide added perks, like notifications when a load is finished and specialty cycles.  What to Look For  ¦ Capacity that matches your needs. Our tests found that washers with a claimed capacity over 4.5 cubic feet readily fit a king-sized comforter.  ¦ A stainless steel tub can withstand higher spin speeds, extracting more water and cutting drying time.  ¦ Look for a machine with an extra rinse cycle if you or others in your household are sensitive to detergent residue. The cycle also helps get rid of pet hair.  What to Skip  ¦ The steam option did boost cleaning slightly in our tests, though washers equipped with that cycle cleaned well overall.  What You'll Pay  Capable washing machines that combine performance and value start at $650 or so. If space is tight, a 24-inchwide compact washer might appeal, but the price isn't right. You'll spend $900 to $2,000 on a compact washer, and roughly the same on a compact dryer.  BUYING ADVICE  If your laundry room is near any family rooms or bedrooms, narrow your search to washing machines that scored Very Good or Excellent in our noise and vibration tests.  For more buying advice, go to CR.org/washers.  Tested models in performance order.  Brand & Model  Overall Score  Test Results  ill s:l  FRONT-LOAD WASHERS  Maytag Maxima MHW8200FW  LG WM9000HVA ID  $1150 0 $1350 ©  ©  ©  70 105  4.5 5.2  'This washer is several inches wider and deeper than most other washers. iDue to reliability issues, Consumer Reports cannot recommend Samsung high-efficiency top-loaders at this time.  _^_^_^_^H  _^-^__H  Brand & Model  Overall Score  Price  Test Results  CD CC  -_c (th a:  0)  o  c  = _!  lc O </)*-  5 a  >¦ o  S.s  UJ to  >¦ U  _= -_ V So rait 3 Q>  UJ  c  c aj O  0J  O  z  Vibration  Cycle time (min.)  -3  TJ >¦  Q) ?  c *¦» O o  FRONT-LOAD WASHERS Continued  9  3  Samsung IT^-^-^-M WF45K6500AW l-B-^-^-M  $750  ©  ©  ©  ©  e  ©  100  4.5  ©  4  Samsung  FlexWash IT  WV60M9900AV  $1710  e  ©  ©  e  e  e  100  5.0  ©  5  Maytag IT^-i-B-H MHW3505FW l_B_^_^__M  $650  e  ©  ©  o  o  ©  85  4.4  ©  6  Samsung rT_^__^__H WF50K7500AW liE-^-^-M  $1080  ©  ©  ©  ©  e  e  100  5  9  7  Kenmore Elite IT-^-H-i-H 41072 IX-^-^-M  $1260  ©  ©  e  e  e  e  95  5.2  ©  8  LGWM5000HWA EE..-H-HI  $1050  e  ©  ©  ©  e  e  105  4.5  ©  9  10  LG Signature r"__^__H__i WM9S00HKA 31 U-^-^--M  $1800  ©  ©  ©  ©  ©  e  120  5.8  0  LGWM5005HKA EHBB  $1500  e  ©  ©  e  e  e  75  4.5  ©  11  LG WM4370HWA rJHB  $850  e  ©  ©  ©  e  ©  75 4.5  ©  12  Samsung  FlexWash M WV55M9600AW  $1450  e  0  e  e  o  ©  95  5.5  TOP-LOAD HIGH-EFFICIENCY WASHERS  1  Samsung r~-_^-^_B WA45K7600AW l-5-^-^-B  $500  ©  ©  ©  ©  o  e  75 4.5  2  Samsung F7_^^^H WA52J8700AP J -*--^-^-i  $1200  ©  ©  ©  ©  ©  ©  75  5.2  3  Samsung C~l_MH-i WA52J8060AW U--^-^-i  $950  ©  ©  e  o  e  ©  75  5.2  4  Samsung FZ^-^-^H WA45H7000AW U-^-^-B  $450  O  ©  e  e  e  ©  80  4.5  5  LGWT7500CW EZ3H.I  $800  ©  ©  e  ©  ©  ©  80  5.2  6  Kenmore Elite ETH-i-^-H 31552 l_!_^_^_l  $850  o  e  ©  ©  e  e  75  5.2  7  LG WT7600HWA EZ-HHH  $1100  ©  ©  e  o  ©  e  75  5.2  8  Whirlpool Cabrio rr-^^M WTW8500DW I-S-^-^-l  $900  e  ©  e  ©  ©  e  80  5.3  © ©  ©  CR BEST BUY  RECOMMENDED  I  Brand S Model  "core" Price Test Resu,ts  ?.__  £  i  C  o  c  _?{=  1c o  >o  o  c  11  (A  0)  c .£  c  ¦  'o  c o  K  _Q  0  E o.E  3  -o£r  OJ ?  O-  Q=  _S a  LU 09  5 a>  o  z  =>  u u  TOP-LOAD HIGH-EFFICIENCY WASHERS Continued  9  Kenmore 28132 ^_H  $700  ©  ©  ©  O  ©  ©J60  5.3  10  Maytag Bravos iKa^B MVWB855DW 14-^-^-1  $1035  ©  ©  ©  O  ©  © 80  5.3  11  LG WT1150CW [__¦__¦  $630  ©  ©  G  ©  ©  ©I 75  4.5  12  Kenmore 26132 E_S1  $550  ©  ©  ©  o  ©  ©60 4.8  13  Kenmore 27132 CK-H-I  $600  ©  ©  ©  ©  ©  © I 60 4.8  COMPACT WASHERS  Botch 800 Series  WAT28402UC  Electrolux  EIFLS20QSW  Kenmore 41912  Mlele W3048  Samsung  WW22K6800AW GE  WCVH4800KWW Asko XL Series W8844XLW  LG WM1377HW Asko W6424W  LG WM1388HW  Blomberg  WM98400SX  Whirlpool  WFW5090GW  $1260  ©  G  G  O  G  $900  Q  ©  ©  ©  ©  $880  ©  ©  ©  O  O  $2000  ©  ©  O  o  G  $900  ©  G  G  ©  ©  $900  O  G  G  G  ©  $2300  ©  O  ©  ©  ©  $900  ©  G  G  G  O  $900  o  ©  ©  O  ©  $900  ©  ©  G  G  ©  $1200  o  ©  ©  O  ©  $940  ©  ©  G  ©  ©  60 110 110 85 100 65 145 75 75 75 95  ©: 55  2.2 2.4 2.4 2.0 2.2 2.2 2.7 2.3 2.0 2.3 2.5 2.3  © ©  o © ©  EXCELLENT  CR BEST BUY  RECOMMENDED  Guide to the Ratings  Overall Score is based mainly on washing ability, efficiency, and noise. The displayed score is out of a total of 100 points. Washing Performance reflects the degree of stain removal from fabric using the most aggressive normal cycle. Energy Efficiency is based on the energy needed to heat the water using a warm wash and cold rinse, to run the washer, and to spin remaining moisture content out at the end of a cycle. Water Efficiency is based on total water used when washing our 8-pound load. Models that earned lower scores for Gentleness are more likely to treat your clothes roughly, causing wear and tear. Noise reflects panelists' judgments during the fill, agitate, and spin cycles. Vibration reflects usage on a suspended wooden floor. Cycle Time (min.) is rounded to the nearest 5 minutes. Claimed Capacity is based on claimed tub volume. Price is approximate retail.  Most & Least Reliable  Percentage likely to break by fifth year of ownership.  FRONT-LOADERS  LG  14%  Kenmore  17%  Maytag  17%  Electrolux  18%  Samsung  18%  Whirlpool  20%  GE  20%  Frigidoire  25%  HIGH-EFFICIENCY TOP-LOADERS  LG  14%  Maytag  16%  GE  16%  Kenmore  18%  Whirlpool  19%  Samsung  23%  LG is tops in reliability among high-efficiency top-loaders and front-loaders, but its breakage rate is not meaningfully lower than those of most competitor brands. Samsung is a less reliable brand among high-efficiency top-loaders. And due to its breakage rate, Samsung high-efficiency top-loaders can't be recommended by Consumer Reports at this time. Frigidaire is the least reliable front-loader brand. And due to its breakage rate, Frigidaire front-loaders also can't be recommended by Consumer Reports at this time.  These conclusions are based on our breakage-rate estimates for high-efficiency toploading and front-loading washing machines by the fifth year of ownership, gathered from 22,494 subscribers who purchased a new high-efficiency top-loading washer and 33,549 subscribers who purchased a new front-loading washer between 2009 and 2016. Our statistical model estimates breakage rates for washers that are not covered by o service contract and accounts for the number of loads of laundry run through the machines per week. Differences of fewer than 5 points between brands are not meaningful. Models within a brand may vary, and changes in design or manufacturer may affect future reliability. Still, choosing a brand with a lower estimated breakage rate can improve your odds of getting a dependable model.  Source: 2016 Fall Product Reliability Survey, Consumer Reports National Research Center.]]></body>
</article>
<article>
<id>2f809458-4c1f-4896-8a47-d51418a348aa</id>
<media_type>Print</media_type>
<title><![CDATA[Trending in the Kitchen]]></title>
<outlet>NEW ENGLAND HOME MAGAZINE</outlet>
<journalist><![CDATA[]]></journalist>
<pubvalue>6574.2300</pubvalue>
<content_summary><![CDATA[Projects We LOVE  ii ii i in n n 11 mi 11 in i mi mi i in i nun  11111111111 n  M II I Ml I I II I I II ' I I I I I II I I II II I II II I ...]]></content_summary>
<content_date>12/1/2017</content_date>
<content_url><![CDATA[http://images.burrellesluce.com/image/2253DA/2253DA_14532]]></content_url>
<city>BOSTON</city>
<state>MA</state>
<body><![CDATA[<p>Trending in the Kitchen</p>Projects We LOVE  ii ii i in n n 11 mi 11 in i mi mi i in i nun  11111111111 n  M II I Ml I I II I I II ' I I I I I II I I II II I II II I Mil I I I II I I i II I I I II I I I II I I I II I I I II I I I II II I II II I III I I II I I I II II Ml I I Ml I I I I I I II I I II I I :  I I I I I II I I I II I I Ii II I M II I II III I I III I I I I I I II II I I I I I II I I < II I I I II M I II II M I I II I I I I M M I I I II I I I I II I I I I I I I I I I I I I I I I I II II I I I II I I I I I I I II I I I I M I I I I I  How is this project unique?  Every project that we work on allows us to be creative in different ways. Design aesthetics can range from traditional to contemporary, and the challenge is selecting products that meet the needs of both function and design.  What were the clients' goals for this project?  Clients want to create a space that will stand the test of time. Jenn-Air appliances incorporate the latest technology and cutting-edge designs without sacrificing quality. Keeping a client's goal in mind is of utmost importance for the lifecycle of the project.  Did you break any "design rules" on this project?  Many homeowners keep their kitchen looking fresh and vibrant by adding a pop of color to an accent wall or by selecting colorfully coordinated cookware and small appliances. Building on this trend, a pop of color in a non-traditional space such as the exterior door of a range or interior of a fridge is a fun and unexpected design detail. The dazzling Obsidian interior offered in some JennAir refrigerators illuminates food under LED lighting to showcase vibrant colors.  Why do you love this project?  Whether you're remodeling your entire  kitchen or looking to add a single upgrade, selecting products reflects your sense of style. Consider all the ways you can enhance your kitchen with these functional additions:  ? Warming drawers provide a great way to keep prepared food hot and fresh.  ? Steam ovens use steam to preserve nutrients in vegetables and tenderness in meats, and convection for evenly baked pastries and roasts. The versatility of steam and convection together creates a dish that's tender inside and roasted or crisped outside.  ? Built-in coffee systems provide baristastyle coffee and free up counter space. Most models also provide instant hot water for teas, soups, and other hot dishes.]]></body>
</article>
<article>
<id>330ce0ec-00b8-4dff-828f-a0c152b1ab3a</id>
<media_type>Print</media_type>
<title><![CDATA[Amazon or Walmart? Some retailers are choosing sides]]></title>
<outlet>JOURNAL-NEWS</outlet>
<journalist><![CDATA[Anne D'Innocenzio]]></journalist>
<pubvalue>360.0000</pubvalue>
<content_summary><![CDATA[RETAII    By Anne D'innocenzio  Associated Press  NEW YORK ? Store chains feeling the upheaval in retail are making strategic alliances ? ...]]></content_summary>
<content_date>11/15/2017</content_date>
<content_url><![CDATA[http://images.burrellesluce.com/image/2253DA/2253DA_14533]]></content_url>
<city>HAMILTON</city>
<state>OH</state>
<body><![CDATA[<p>Amazon or Walmart? Some retailers are choosing sides</p>RETAII  Amazon or Walmart? Some retailers are choosing sides  By Anne D'innocenzio  Associated Press  NEW YORK ? Store chains feeling the upheaval in retail are making strategic alliances ? and that can mean picking sides.  Kohl's shoppers can find Amazon devices at some stores, and return items they bought from the online retailer. Nike has made some of its sneakers available through Amazon. The owner of Sears is selling Kenmore-branded appliances on Amazon in some markets. And Best Buy is teaming up with Amazon for voice shopping.  Meanwhile, Walmart, which has the most store locations, is assembling a coalition of its own: buying smaller online brands and becoming the highest-profile partner to Google in voice shopping. And the discount chain that touts low prices announced a web partnership Monday with high-end department store Lord & Taylor.  "When you are in an historic uncharted chaotic situation, you often see these strange bedfellows," said Joel Bines, co-head of AlixPartners' retail practice and a managing director at the firm.  Since the beginning of the year, several retailers have filed for bankruptcy protection, including well-known names like Toys R Us. And retailers have announced thousands of store closings, with more expected. Analysts say some brands realize they might not succeed alone.  "You have to be challenging accepted norms. So you might find partners that you normally wouldn't have considered," said Wendy Liebmann, CEO of WSL Strategic Retail. "This has exploded because of the urgency to change. You look at retailers who are closing or struggling."  So as Amazon moves even further into fashion, home electronics and grocery stores, and cements shopper loyalty with its $99-a-year Prime membership, stores are developing partnerships with the online retailer to increase customer traffic or expand their offerings online.  At the participating Kohl's stores, shoppers will find 1,000-square-foot Amazon areas that sell Echos, Fire tablets and other gadgets.  People can also arrange to have an Amazon employee visit their home and install a device or rec¬  ommend smart home products to buy. And some stores pack and ship eligible Amazon return items for free. Kohl's hopes the arrangement brings in shoppers who might pick up clothes or home items.  Analysts say other department stores, facing the same kind of issues, could follow.  From its base with 4,700 U.S. stores, Walmart is lining up other partners. In voice shopping, it hooked up with Google, which has signed up other chains such as Target and Home Depot to fight the dominance of Amazon's Alexa-powered Echo devices.  Lord & Taylor's president Liz Rodbell said the arrangement with Walmart allows the chain to attract new customers who already are buying higher-end products on Walmart.com.  She called the partnership "a pivotal moment" for the retailer. It comes after the chain's parent company announced last month it was selling its New York flagship building to We Work and leasing back a portion of the space.  Since the $3 billion-plus acquisition ofjet.com last year, Walmart has bought several online brands like Bonobos and ModCloth.  Sears' owner is selling Kenmore appliances on Amazon in some markets, while Kohl's and Nike have formed alliances with the giant. Meanwhile, Walmart is buying smaller online brands and becoming the highest-profile partner to Google in voice shopping, rick bowmer/ap]]></body>
</article>
<article>
<id>e727015f-2c09-4878-817a-927384226c1e</id>
<media_type>Print</media_type>
<title><![CDATA[More retailers picking sides to form strategic alliances]]></title>
<outlet>HERALD</outlet>
<journalist><![CDATA[Anne D'Innocenzio]]></journalist>
<pubvalue>1817.1600</pubvalue>
<content_summary><![CDATA[BY ANNE D'INNOCENZIO  Associated Press NEW YORK  Store chains feeling the upheaval in retail are making strategic alliances - and that ...]]></content_summary>
<content_date>11/19/2017</content_date>
<content_url><![CDATA[http://images.burrellesluce.com/image/2253DA/2253DA_14521]]></content_url>
<city>ROCK HILL</city>
<state>SC</state>
<body><![CDATA[<p>More retailers picking sides to form strategic alliances</p>More retailers picking sides to form strategic alliances  BY ANNE D'INNOCENZIO  Associated Press NEW YORK  Store chains feeling the upheaval in retail are making strategic alliances - and that can mean picking sides.  Kohl's shoppers can find Amazon devices at some stores, and return items they bought from the online retailer. Nike has made some of its sneakers available through Amazon. The owner of Sears is selling Kenmore-branded appliances on Amazon in some markets. And Best Buy is teaming up with Amazon for voice shopping.  Meanwhile, Walmart, which has the most store locations, is assembling a coalition of its own: buying smaller online brands and becoming the highestprofile partner to Google in voice shopping. And the discount chain that touts low prices announced a web partnership this past week with high-end department store Lord & Taylor.  "When you are in an historic uncharted chaotic situation, you often see these strange bedfellows," said Joel Bines, co-head of AlixPartners' retail practice and a managing director at the firm.  Since the beginning of the year, several retailers have filed for bankruptcy protection, including wellknown names like Toys R Us. And retailers have announced thousands of  store closings, with more expected. Analysts say some brands realize they might not succeed alone.  "You have to be challenging accepted norms. So you might find partners that you normally wouldn't have considered," said Wendy Liebmann, CEO of WSL Strategic Retail. "This has exploded because of the urgency to change. You look at retailers who are closing or struggling."  So as Amazon moves even further into fashion, home electronics and grocery stores, and cements shopper loyalty with its $99-a-year Prime membership, stores are developing partnerships with the online retailer to increase customer traffic or expand their offerings online.  At the participating Kohl's stores, shoppers will find 1,000-square-foot Amazon areas that sell Echos, Fire tablets and other gadgets. People can also arrange to have an Amazon employee visit their home and install a device or recommend smart home products to buy. And some stores pack and ship eligible Amazon return items for free. Kohl's hopes the arrangement brings in shoppers who might pick up clothes or home items.  Analysts say other department stores, facing the same kind of issues, could follow.  From its base with 4,700 U.S. stores, Walmart is  lining up other partners. In voice shopping, it hooked up with Google, which has signed up other chains such as Target and Home Depot to fight the dominance of Amazon's Alexapowered Echo devices.  Lord & Taylor's president Liz Rodbell told The Associated Press the arrangement with Walmart allows the chain to attract new customers who already are buying higherend products on Walmart.com. She called the partnership "a pivotal moment" for the retailer. It comes after the chain's parent company announced last month it was selling its New York flagship building to We Work and leasing back a portion of the space.  Neither company would say the financial details of the arrangement.  Denise Incandela, head of fashion at Walmart's U.S. e-commerce division, says it's focusing on specialized shopping experiences, starting with fashion. Since the $3 billionplus acquisition ofjet.com last year, Walmart has bought several online brands like Bonobos and ModCloth.  Analysts say Walmart is developing its own higherend online mall as a way to counter Amazon's dominance. Bines said it's a good strategy, since Walmart.com could attract "an entirely different demographic" from the chain's physical stores.  Walmart store customers have a median household income of about $48,000, below the $56,000 for walmart.com customers, according to Craig Johnson, president of the retail consulting group Customer Growth Partners. Amazon.com shoppers have a median income of $85,000, Johnson esti¬  mates.  Liebmann says the bigger question is whether there would be any resistance from Lord & Taylor shoppers. Bonobos and ModCloth fans complained vociferously on social media when reports were swirling about Walmart's move to buy the brands. "It has to be pre¬  sented well," Liebmann said.  Overall, Bines expects Amazon and Walmart to announce more partnerships. "In the next two or three years, companies will chose sides," he said. "But after that, the lines will be blurred."  JOHNRAOUX AP  Store chains watching the upheaval in retail are making strategic alliances. For example, Kohl's shoppers can find Amazon devices at some stores. For Kohl's, the Amazon partnership offers lots of potential: It pulls online and voice shoppers into the stores where they might pick up clothes or home items.]]></body>
</article>
<article>
<id>1137ec05-a04d-4003-9379-ed8866cb385b</id>
<media_type>Print</media_type>
<title><![CDATA[More retailers picking sides to form strategic alliances]]></title>
<outlet>HERALD</outlet>
<journalist><![CDATA[Anne D'Innocenzio]]></journalist>
<pubvalue>2677.9200</pubvalue>
<content_summary><![CDATA[BY ANNE D'INNOCENZIO  Associated Press NEWYORK  Store chains feeling the upheaval in retail are making strategic alliances and that can ...]]></content_summary>
<content_date>11/19/2017</content_date>
<content_url><![CDATA[http://images.burrellesluce.com/image/2253DA/2253DA_14519]]></content_url>
<city>ROCK HILL</city>
<state>SC</state>
<body><![CDATA[<p>More retailers picking sides to form strategic alliances</p>More retailers picking sides to form strategic alliances  BY ANNE D'INNOCENZIO  Associated Press NEWYORK  Store chains feeling the upheaval in retail are making strategic alliances and that can mean picking sides.  Kohl's shoppers can find Amazon devices at some stores, and return items they bought from the online retailer. Nike has made some of its sneakers available through Amazon. The owner of Sears is selling Kenmore-branded appliances on Amazon in some markets. And Best Buy is teaming up with Amazon for voice shopping.  Meanwhile, Walmart, which has the most store locations, is assembling a coalition of its own: buying smaller online brands and becoming the highestprofile partner to Google in voice shopping. And the discount chain that touts low prices announced a web partnership this past week with high-end department store Lord & Taylor.  "When you are in an historic uncharted chaotic situation, you often see these strange bedfellows," said Joel Bines, co-head of AlixPartners' retail practice and a managing director at the firm.  Since the beginning of the year, several retailers have filed for bankruptcy protection, including wellknown names like Toys R Us. And retailers have announced thousands of  store closings, with more expected. Analysts say some brands realize they might not succeed alone.  "You have to be challenging accepted norms. So you might find partners that you normally wouldn't have considered," said Wendy Liebmann, CEO of WSL Strategic Retail. "This has exploded because of the urgency to change. You look at retailers who are closing or struggling."  So as Amazon moves even further into fashion, home electronics and grocery stores, and cements shopper loyalty with its $99-a-year Prime membership, stores are developing partnerships with the online retailer to increase customer traffic or expand their offerings online.  At the participating Kohl's stores, shoppers will find 1,000-squarefoot Amazon areas that sell Echos, Fire tablets and other gadgets. People can also arrange to have an Amazon employee visit their home and install a device or recommend smart home products to buy. And some stores pack and ship eligible Amazon return items for free. Kohl's hopes the arrangement brings in shoppers who might pick up clothes or home items.  Analysts say other department stores, facing the same kind of issues, could follow.  From its base with  4,700 U.S. stores, Walmart is lining up other partners. In voice shopping, it hooked up with Google, which has signed up other chains such as Target and Home Depot to fight the dominance of Amazon's Alexa-powered Echo devices.  Lord & Taylor's president Liz Rodbell told The Associated Press the arrangement with Walmart allows the chain to attract new customers who already are buying higherend products on Walmart.com. She called the partnership "a pivotal moment" for the retailer. It comes after the chain's parent company announced last month it was selling its New York flagship building to We Work and leasing back a portion of the space.  Neither company would say the financial details of the arrangement.  Denise Incandela, head of fashion at Walmart's U.S. e-commerce division, says it's focusing on specialized shopping experiences, starting with fashion. Since the $3 billionplus acquisition of Jet.com last year, Walmart has bought several online brands like Bonobos and ModCloth.  Analysts say Walmart is developing its own higherend online mall as a way to counter Amazon's dominance. Bines said it's a good strategy, since Walmart.com could attract  "an entirely different demographic" from the chain's physical stores.  Walmart store customers have a median household income of about $48,000, below the $56,000 for walmart.com customers, according to Craig Johnson, president of the retail consulting group Customer Growth Partners. Amazon.com shoppers have a median income of $85,000, Johnson estimates.  Liebmann says the bigger question is whether there would be any resistance from Lord & Taylor shoppers. Bonobos and ModCloth fans com¬  plained vociferously on social media when reports were swirling about Walmart's move to buy the brands. "It has to be presented well," Liebmann said.  Overall, Bines expects Amazon and Walmart to announce more partnerships. "In the next two or three years, companies will chose sides," he said. "But after that, the lines will be blurred."  YOU HAVE TO BE CHALLENGING ACCEPTED NORMS. SO YOU MIGHT FIND PARTNERS  THAT YOU NORMALLY WOULDN'T HAVE CONSIDERED. THIS HAS EXPLODED BECAUSE OF THE URGENCY TO CHANGE. YOU LOOK AT RETAILERS WHO ARE CLOSING OR STRUGGLING.  Wendy Liebmann, CEO of WSL Strategic Retail  JOHN RAOUX AP  Store chains watching the upheaval in retail are making strategic alliances. For example, Kohl's shoppers can find Amazon devices at some stores. For Kohl's, the Amazon partnership offers lots of potential: It pulls online and voice shoppers into the stores where they might pick up clothes or home items.  JULIO CORTEZ AP  Walmart announced last week that it will devote a section on its website to upscale Lord & Taylor, the latest strategic partnership as retailers make alliances.  RICKBOWMER AP  Strategic alliances are changing the retail industry. For example, the parent company of Sears is selling Kenmore-branded appliances on Amazon in some markets.]]></body>
</article>
</articles>
